If you are arguing with them or you
disagree with them, you know, you got
pretty much fired very quickly. Trump
called TSMC, Taiwan Semiconductor, the
most powerful company. And in March, we
see that he announced that TSMC is going
to invest a hundred um billion dollars
in US Arizona. And that worried a lot of
people because
longterm over 5 years Bitcoin will be
the money printers turned on not only
here in the United States but around the
world. I think as I've gotten older I
realized that the smartest people don't
churn a lot. They just sit tight in
really good assets. The one thing that
you really have to do philosophically in
life is how do you think Bitcoin will do
2025 2026? Bitcoin will get to
the king of Toronto.
Bonnie,
we're at the digital asset summit in New
York and we're going to be talking about
what's next for cryptocurrencies, the
geopolitical landscape. What's next for
the economy? Anthony Scaramucci joins us
today. He is the founder of Skybridge
Capital. Very honored to host Anthony.
I'm David Lynn, host of the David Lynn
Report. Bonnie from Bonnie Blockchain.
Anthony, so good to see you. You are so
good at this, David. That means I mean I
try to keep this the staccato delivery
and that was fantastic. Yes. High praise
coming from you wellon host and uh my
co-host for uh the show Bonnie
Blockchain. She has an awesome channel
but uh let's start with some stuff on uh
tariffs. Bonnie take it away. We have a
lot of audience from Taiwan from the a
from Asia Chinese speaking region. So in
case they're not familiar with American
politics, you were in the White House
for 11 days. Yeah. And um I got
unceremoniously fired after the 11 days.
It was a fun 11 days though, I will say.
Right. So, how is working with President
Trump? I want to ask you about his um
terror. So, working with President Trump
on the campaign was actually a lot of
fun. I always like to tell people very
candidly what it was like. It was a lot
of fun. He's a he's a he's a jocular
guy, geralous. He has a good sense of
humor. He can be very witty. He's
probably the most famous stand-up
comedian in the world if you really
think about his personality. But when he
got to the White House, he got a little
bit tighter, a little more imperious,
and it became a little less fun. And
then if you were arguing with him or you
disagree with them, you know, you got
pretty much fired very quickly. And so
we argued about a few things. I shortly
thereafter got fired. So no hard
feelings on that. I just want to, you
know, address policy and talk about what
I like and what I don't like. So, you
want to talk about the tariffs? Yeah.
Markets don't like uncertainty, right?
And do you think that's a bargaining
chip? Is he forcing us into a recession?
What's going on?
Well, oh, let let's give the optimistic
case first and then we'll talk a little
bit about what could could happen, but
he's already sort of he's already heard
America in a number of different ways
because when you start out with that
sort of fire and bellacosity of
rhetoric, uh you're turning people off.
You have the mayor of Toronto as an
example. Now you can't bid if you're an
American company on any Toronto-based
contract. Okay. So it's it has a
chilling effect. If you look at the last
three weeks of market activity, European
markets are up, US markets are down,
flow of funds are moving away from the
United States. And so as the American
president, you sure would want foreign
investment capital flowing into the US.
I think one of the things that has made
the US so attractive globally over the
last 150 years is we have a stable
political system, decentralized system,
lots of checks and balances and a real
platform for a predictable rule of law.
There's not arbitrary and capricious law
here that you sometimes find in regimes
that have less checks and balances. So,
uh, I think when the president is acting
in that way, uh, it's scary to people
and I think it sends the wrong message.
And Winston Churchill had a a great
line. I, uh, there's nothing worse than
fighting with your allies, except when
you have to fight without them, meaning
they're no longer your allies. And so, I
think I think it's dangerous. I don't
like it, just if I'm being brutally
honest about it. Uh but remember the
best outcome could be it's a negotiating
device. You get to the April 2nd
deadline, they declare victory and say
that stuff has been done on the border,
stuff has been done on the Canadian
border related to fent and all stuff has
been done on the Mexican border. Yeah.
Premier Doug Ford wants to cut off
electricity. Canada's fighting back. He
wants to cut off power to the eastern
seabboard. What do you think of that?
Probably a bridge too far. I mean, it
could get to that. I mean, if if if the
the president wants to ramp up his uh
his rhetoric, it could get to that. I
think that the big mistake that
President Trump is making is you're
you're thinking about this in a 1950s
sort of way and we're in 2025 and we're
33 34 years since the signing of NAFTA
and you have fully integrated these two
economies. So, let me give you two
examples. Example number one, I'm a
farmer lobster farmer. I've got lo
lobster farm situation in Maine. I'm
catching the lobster in US water, but
I'm shipping it to a
processor across the border in Canada.
That's 25% tariff. And then it's going
to come back to me processed. So I'm now
going to sell to the restaurants. That's
another 25% tariff. So 25% over, 25%
back. Price of lobster is 50%. You're
going to bankrupt the lobster farmer. Uh
your the crude in Alberta is a heavy
crude. Most of the refineries that are
south of the Canadian border in the
United States are set up to refine that
crude. If you're telling me that the
Alberta premier is going to start
shipping that crude to China, Taiwan,
you pick the area of the world it's
going to ship it to or you're going to
have to retool all the refineries in the
United States. And so president's making
a mistake because these countries are
now fully integrated. So his staff is
now trying to get to him and say, "Okay,
you should probably cool out on this
sort of bellassi of rhetoric and we
should get to whatever you don't like in
the US MCA deal." And the big irony
there, guys, is that he negotiated that
deal. And he said in 2019, this was the
greatest trade deal in history, the US
MCA. So, if you don't like the deal now,
6 years later, let's go through the deal
surgically and pick out the things that
you don't like and let's see if we can
make it better uh for the United States
and acceptable to Canada and Mexico. But
I think the blunt instrument of using
the tariffs the way he's using them is
going to cause a crisis in the United
States. It'll be a further decline in
the stock market. If the tariff talk
persists post April 2nd, further decline
in the stock market, likely recession,
and a further detachment from our more
traditional allies, which even our
adversaries in the world will not like
because it it creates more
unpredictability in the world. I'm going
to come back to what you just said
because Scott had to quote, but I think
uh we want to talk about just finishing
off the trade wars, talk about how it
affects Taiwan and the Asia region. So,
um, Trump called TSMC, Taiwan
Semiconductor, the most powerful
company. And in March, we see that he
announced that TSMC is going to invest a
hundred um billion dollars in US
Arizona. And that worried a lot of
people because it kind of compromised
the silicone shield of Taiwan, right?
What is your thought?
Well, this could be a contrary thought.
I I think that uh long-term thinking
would suggest that uh you need more
stability and you need more peace which
will create greater prosperity. And I
think if you look at mainland China's
economy right now, uh that economy needs
to heal and possibly reset and restart
its growth. Uh uh it has languished for
a few years if you just look at the
data. Again, that's the Chinese
government's data and that could be
understated or overstated, but I'm just
going off of their data. The economy is
not doing as well as they would like it
to be. So I don't it's not clear to me
that the quote unquote silicon shield is
uh is in play at this moment. Um if you
take the argument that the president
wants a multi-olar world where she is
controlling a part of the world and
Putin is controlling a part of the world
and let's say Trump is controlling North
America which in his mind would include
things like Canada and Greenland and
possibly the Panama Canal. And and
you're laughing, Bonnie, because this is
an absurdity to what he's talking about
because this is like 18th century
Prussian colonialism, which isn't really
appropriate for the 21st century. So, so
to me, when I step back and look at the
landscape of the world, uh I don't think
it's in the interest of the mainland
Chinese government, the Communist Party
there to upset the core stability of
what's going on in the world,
particularly when they're under economic
stress. And so, uh, I think whether
people realize this or not, the United
States has to reshore some of its
manufacturing. The United States has to
reshore a lot of their chip
manufacturing, frankly, because it's too
big of a core component to the economy.
And 25 years ago when we were loveydovey
with China and we helped China get into
the World Trade Organization, we thought
we were moving
towards some level of singularity and
some level of a more integrated system
of like and trust with each other, more
harmony, more peace. Remember the the US
mantra for the postw World War II order
was raise living standards around the
world. And if you raise living standards
around the world, you have less
geopolitical conflict. What was left out
of that is that there's still an
ideological struggle going on in the
world and as long as that ideological
struggle is going on there will be a
threat and so the US has to protect
itself by reshoring some things. So I
want to get your prediction on Bitcoin
price. Um how do you think Bitcoin will
do 2025 2026?
I mean you know Bitcoin is being held
back right now by the macro dilemma that
we're facing. You know, I think people
were expecting the President Trump would
be pro business and he'd be pro growth
for the stock market. I don't think they
were ant anticipating these sort of uh
uh starts and stops with the tariffs and
this level of uncertainty. And so, uh if
it go if it gets calmer and it looks
more like the 2017 2021 Trump term, uh
Bitcoin will get to 200,000 this year.
If you're telling me we're going to be
in a protracted trade war and we're
going to be fighting with our European
and Western allies, uh, you know,
Bitcoin will probably hover near here,
maybe gets back to 100,000, but it it's
going to be very hard for Bitcoin to
ascend to where I think it could go uh,
if we were just in a more normal
environment. Normal being proper
intersection between government and and
finance. So just on that note, so you
said earlier we might get a recession.
So this is Scott Bent's quote, Treasur
Treasury uh secretary. What I could
guarantee is we would have had a
financial crisis. I've studied it. I've
taught it. And if we had kept up those
spending levels that everyone knows was
unsustainable,
uh we are resetting and we are putting
things on a sustainable path. That's
what he's talking about for the future.
If he's right and this debt level rise
is not sustainable, what happens to
Bitcoin? What happens to risk assets?
Well, well, long term, Bitcoin is going
to be okay. I I think the question was
what's Bitcoin going to look like at at
the end of the year? And and it'll
really depend on the administration. In
my opinion, if they calm down, Bitcoin
will go to 200,000. Long-term over 5
years, Bitcoin will be several hundred
thousand because the money printers
turned on, not only here in the United
States, but around the world, and people
will start gravitating to Bitcoin
because of the properties associated
with Bitcoin. And we and many people in
our industry believe it's a store of
value. And I think other people will
draw that conclusion as they start to
see these metaphor forces. But but I
think what the secretary is saying is
true. You can't go from $4.5 trillion of
spending and six short years later
you're at 7 trillion on your way to 9
trillion and say that that's
sustainable. It's just just the math
isn't going to work for the United
States. and you'll force more extreme
politics into the country because you're
not going to pay the debt back. Let's
just be honest with everybody. You're
going to monetize that debt. And so what
you'll do is you if you create 8%
inflation in the country, which we had
in 2023, well, you just wiped out 8% of
the country's debt. Okay? You can have
it nominally, but it's it's worth less.
And so so to me uh the right thing to do
is to get the country on a more
sustainable path. But the wrong thing to
do is to push the country into
austerity. If you push the country in
austerity, you'll touch off negative
thinking in the country and you'll touch
off a negative vicious flywheel that
will lead to deconumption and lead to a
recession. So you know this is
gradualism. Governments have to think,
you know, let's let's steal something
from the Chinese for a second. uh the US
government has to think in 10, 15, 20,
possibly 25 year movements. We don't
have a project 2049. Okay? But we need
one, right? And so what is that project?
How do we look over the next 15 years?
You can manage the deficit and you could
reduce the deficit as a percentage of
GDP and you could do it gradually which
wouldn't cause recessionary or austerity
like pain. So, uh, you know, the problem
is you're dealing with the president.
And so, Scott's hamstrung. If if Scott
was dealing with a more rational
political leader, uh, less
self-absorbed, you'd be able to sit down
with him and say, "Okay, here's what we
need to do. return to pay as you go
legislation which worked in the 1990s
benchmark with our colleagues in the in
the Congress certain levels of spending
and this continuing resolution that's
taken place for almost 13 years now in
the American government uh and you can
get things right sized and the markets
would be very satisfied with that. No
one's suggesting that the current
spending should grow and get out of
control, but there's a methodology to
slowing down the spending that won't
over overly hurt the economy, the
markets, or lower middle inome people.
Um, but I'm not going to get a lot of
attention if I'm President Trump saying
all that. It's more interesting and it's
more addictive to go on and off with the
tariffs and get a lot of news attention
and have these sorts of microphones in
my face in the Oval Office all day. Um,
how is Skybridge adjusting the portfolio
after the Bitcoin reserve? So, Skybridge
has had a couple of very good years. I'm
not allowed to talk about the
performance because we're registered,
but I'll just say this. If Bitcoin went
from
16,000 in January of two 2023 to let's
call it 80,000 and Skybridge had a
25ish% position in his overall portfolio
in Bitcoin, you'd have to imagine that
we've had a couple of really good
performance years. And so what I said
from the stage here at DS, and I'll say
to you guys, and I would say it
globally, is that we're going to hold
our Bitcoin position and possibly even
expand our Bitcoin position. And I'll
take the position that Bitcoin may
muddle a little bit this year because of
the metadata and the macroeconomic
forces, but I think it's a probably a 5x
in five years. And so, uh, I'm going to
hold that asset. And I think we're going
to get rewarded for that. Now, will
there be volatility? Sure. Uh, but, you
know, I'm I I I think as I've gotten
older, I realize that the smartest
people don't churn a lot. They just sit
tight in really good assets. I think
that's what Skybridge is going to do
over the next 5 years. Are you hedging
against volatility? I'm not.
Okay. I'm not. Are you still buying at
this price? We are. Okay. I just bought
some recently at this price. I think
we'll wrap up with a few questions about
you, Anthony. Yeah. Audience wants to
learn about you and your journey to
success. I was 6'4 when I met Donald
Trump. And look at me now. Right. That's
what we'll start with. Okay. Go ahead,
Bonnie. Well, I was preparing for this
interview and I watched one of your
interviews. You said you are from a
middle class family and your dad was a
crane operator and you're super mega
successful right now. If you could go
back and meet your younger self, what
would you say to it?
Well, you know, listen, I I look, I I
it's a great question, but I think that
the one thing that you really have to do
philosophically in life is not look
back. I think what sometimes happens and
the great Chinese philosopher Laauo Zoo
once said if I look back you can
sometimes think about things that you
made mistakes in you can fill your mind
with regret you become depressed if you
look forward you could get anxious about
the future because the future's
uncertain we don't know what's coming
and so the best thing you could do is
live in the present but what I what I
would say to you guys is if I could look
back I would get on the phone with
myself or get face to face with myself
and I grab myself by the collar taller
body and I'd say take more risk, be more
confident, be more sure of yourself
because when you grow up the way I did,
you're you're born with some inherent
insecurities related
to the corporate environment. You know,
my dad was a blueco collar worker. I
never saw the inside of a country club,
never hit a golf ball, never swung a
tennis racket, never saw a building like
this when I was a kid or been in a
commercial office building. And so it is
daunting and it is intimidating
uh because you have to make that
transition. It's almost like a right of
passage. And I think I would tell my
younger self to be way more confident
than I actually was. And it's it's it's
okay to be confident. Doesn't mean to be
arrogant, but you could it's okay to
like believe in yourself. Well, you're
one of the most confident, successful
people we know. Anthony, thank you so
much for coming on the show. Pleasure.
You already had a lot. She's so funny.
This is so impressive. Are you not Are
you not impressed with this? I am very
He slooked us out of the slicked us out
of the interview and it's really good.
Thank you.